fnews.com 2015-06-27

# #fnews

### About #fnews

#fnews is a social news filtering application that allows you to "follow your news":

We filter news based on their #hashtags.  
We filter news based on their #trendiness  
We filter news based on their #popularity.  
You filter news based on your #hashtags & **create your own #fnews page**.

**Sign up to create your #fnews page now** , start following your news based on your hashtags & share your #fnews page with the world. 

### Contact #fnews

You can contact #fnews via:

\- Email at webmaster@fnews.com

\- Mail at fnews, 45B West Wilmot Street, Richmond Hill, Ontario L4B 2P3, Canada

### Disclaimer

The information contained in this website is for general information purposes only. The information is provided by #fnews and while we endeavour to keep the information up to date and correct, we make no representations or warranties of any kind, express or implied, about the completeness, accuracy, reliability, suitability or availability with respect to the website or the information, products, services, or related graphics contained on the website for any purpose. Any reliance you place on such information is therefore strictly at your own risk.

In no event will we be liable for any loss or damage including without limitation, indirect or consequential loss or damage, or any loss or damage whatsoever arising from loss of data or profits arising out of, or in connection with, the use of this website.

Through this website you are able to link to other websites which are not under the control of #fnews. We have no control over the nature, content and availability of those sites. The inclusion of any links does not necessarily imply a recommendation or endorse the views expressed within them.

Every effort is made to keep the website up and running smoothly. However, #fnews takes no responsibility for, and will not be liable for, the website being temporarily unavailable due to technical issues beyond our control.

Any use or distribution of content produced by the editors of this website in coursework, essays or other school or college work is strictly prohibited.

### Privacy Policy

If you require any more information or have any questions about our privacy policy, please feel free to contact us by email at webmaster@fnews.com.

At #fnews, the privacy of our visitors is of extreme importance to us. This privacy policy document outlines the types of personal information is received and collected by #fnews and how it is used.

Log Files

Like many other Web sites, #fnews makes use of log files. The information inside the log files includes internet protocol ( IP ) addresses, type of browser, Internet Service Provider ( ISP ), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user’s movement around the site, and gather demographic information. IP addresses, and other such information are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable.

Cookies and Web Beacons

#fnews does use cookies to store information about visitors preferences, record user-specific information on which pages the user access or visit, customize Web page content based on visitors browser type or other information that the visitor sends via their browser.

Some of our advertising partners may use cookies and web beacons on our site.

These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to the advertisements and links that appear on #fnews send directly to your browsers. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. Other technologies ( such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons ) may also be used by the third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and / or to personalize the advertising content that you see.

#fnews has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers.

You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices. #fnews's privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites.

If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers' respective websites.
